

APICHET NUAMTUN

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I have experience working with both websites and mobile applications using the React framework. I am currently working as a FullStack Developer at 3i infotech on-site True Corporation, improving website and API services in sales campaigns to company clients. And I used to work as a freelancer building a mobile learning app called archiveNex app. You can find and download it in the App Store and Google Play Store.

Competencies: ReactJs/React Native Framework: React,Redux/Mobx,GoLang Language: Javascript,Css,Python,Java

Statement: Higher-Order Components (Hoc), Material UI,

Style -component

Tool: Jira, Tello, Bitbucket, GitLab, GitHub Services: Jenkins, Kibana, Kong Services

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS













CONTACT DETAILS

Mobile: 083-982-8552 JobsDB: Apichet Nuamtun LineID: oatporn112 Slack: Apichet (OatSmith) LinkedIN: Apichet Nuamtun E-mail: anuamtoon@gmail.com

CHARACTER REFERENCES

Asst.. Prof. Dr. Chatklaw Jareonpon
Director of PhD. Program in Cs Director of Computer
Center, Mahasarakham University
Cell: 098-595-1653
Email: chatklaw.j@msu.ac.th

Asst. Prof. Suchart Khummanee
Head of Depament, Mahasarakham University
Cell: 084-875-5582
Email: suchart.k@msu.ac.th

Mr. Jatuphon Khotsopha (Man) Business & Integration Arch Analyst (IT-ONE)

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER (REACT, GOLANG)

True Corporation Jun 2021 to Present



- I've been tasked with overseeing both FE issues developed with ReactJs, Redux based stores, and BE written for development with Golang, and I've also been tasked with overseeing the deployment. EnvTest/Production with Jenkins and I can use Kibana to view the logs of each team project repository and I can also use Kong to create an API route service.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER (REACT)

Can Innovation Co., Ltd. November 2020 to Jun 2021

It's developed with active at work that cannot only develop the system but also understand the business and provide sincere service to customers.

My experience is developing Websites and Applications using **ReactJs** and **React Native**







Checkadi.c

WebAdmin MitrApp

FRONTEND DEVELOPER (REACT NATIVE)

Freelancer Mar 2021 to Jun 2021



- It's an application about teaching and learning and is also an application that will help increase the skills of students in various fields because in this application there are various cross videos to learn. You can also join meetings and open online lessons. (Before you can enter this app, you must be a member)

DATA ENGINEER

Hydro-Informatics Intitute June 2020 to November 2020



- Overseeing analyzing and management current state of water in rice fields. and SWAT (soil and water assessment tool) model using for analysis water balance of 25 watershed area in Thailand developer (Python Postgresql)

EDUCATION HISTORY

MAHASARAKHAM UNIVERSITY (2016-2020)

- Faculty of Informatics Computer Science

NONG RUEA WHITTIYA HIGH SCHOOL (2010-2016)

- Sciences and Mathematics Program

GRADUATE PROJECT

AQUAPONICS MANAGEMENT SYSTEM BY INTERNET OF THINGS (IOT)

- It's a mix during hydroponic plants and raising fish in the pond therefore brought in the internet of things (iot) to control the growth of fish and plants





